Guide to the Martin Sedlazek NASA Collection, 1953-1999
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 1 Introduction and Summary - 1st Edition, December 13, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Space Station System Requirements Document - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force Concept Development Group, December 25, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Space Station Review to Mr. Culbertson - Associate Deputy Administrator, December 1983 - January 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Advancing Automation and Robotics Technology for the Space Station and for the U.S. Economy - A Technical Report, Volume II, March 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Advancing Automation and Robotics Technology for the Space Station and for the U.S. Economy - Executive Overview - Volume I, March 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Space Station Program Description Document with Books 1-7 Titles - Final Edition Cover, March 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 7 Program Plan - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force - Final Edition, March 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Distribution Note from Lyn D. Wigbels, June 27, 1985, Concerning and Attached to Research on Multinational Enterprises Experience Relevant to International Partnerships for Space Station - Summary Report, August 1984 - January 1985, August 1984 - January 1985, June 27, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Draft Final - Summary Report of the Space Station Operation Task Force, August 28, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- The Planetary Report Magazine - Volume X, Number 3, May/June, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Design Guidelines for Robotic Serviceable Instruments - Preliminary Guidelines Document, August 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Saturn V Flight Manual - SA 509, August 15, 1969, Changed January 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Current News - Apollo 11 Special - Part 1, July - August, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Space Station Reference Configuration - Systems Engineering and Integration Space Station Program Office - Pages 1 - 400, August 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Space Station Reference Configuration - Systems Engineering and Integration Space Station Program Office - Pages 401 - 786, August 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Station Keeping Platform - Feasibility Study - Final Report, June 19, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Utilization of Space Station Freedom (SSF) Platform Hardware to Support Initial SSF Assembly, March 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Code E Space Station Pointer System Study - Study Team Final Report, January 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Space Station, December 4, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Space Station Freedom Program - Goddard Space Flight Center - Associate Administrator's Review by James Moore, February 28, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Space Station Management Plan and Procurement Strategy, December 14, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Folder Containing Photographs and Information on Mariner Mars 1969, December 15, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Ranger 1964-65 Informational Report, July 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Building Blocks to Space Informational Report, circa 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Aerospace Management Quarterly, Summer 1966, Volume 1, Number 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Propulsion For Deep Space Informational Report, June 1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Report from Mars - Mariner IV - Two Copies, 1964 - 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- National Geographic Magazine - Featuring "Voyage to the Planets" Article, August 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Testimony to the U.S. Senate - Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences - "The Pioneering Phase of our Expansion into Space" by Harrison H. Schmitt, Tuesday, April 10, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Statement of Willis H. Shapley Associate Deputy Administrator - National Aeronautics and Space Administration before the Subcommittee on Africa - Committee on Foreign Affairs - House of Representatives, circa 1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- NASA Photograph - Earth from Space?, circa 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- NASA Photograph - Group of Men with Respective Signatures Below - Eleven Copies, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Project Gemini - A Chronology, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Microgravity - Informational Report, circa 1985? (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer (FTS) In-House Phase B Study Results, April 29, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Flight Telerobotic Service - In-House Phase B Study - First NASA/Industry Briefing - Goddard Space Flight Center, December 14-15, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Managing NASA in the Apollo Era, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Aviation Week and Space Technology Magazine - "Commercialization of Space", June 25, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- NASA Memoranda and Agreements Regarding the Space Station, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Space Station - Phase C/D/E Agreements, December 1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Distribution Note on MOU Reference Package, January 4, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Memorandum of Understanding Between the United States National Aeronautics and Space Administration and the European Space Agency on Cooperation in the Detailed Design, Development, Operation and Utilization of the Permanently Manned Civil Space Station with Memoranda Attached, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Memorandum of Understanding Between the United States National Aeronautics and Space Administration and the European Space Agency on Cooperation in the Detailed Design, Development, Operation and Utilization of the Permanently Manned Civil Space Station with Memoranda Attached, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Attachment 2 - Amendment of Article 12 of the NASA/STA MOU, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Lessons for the Space Station: JPL's Perspective on the Shuttle Payload Process, March 1, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- NASA Space Station Freedom User Utilization Project Office - SSF Payload Integration Group White Paper - Final Draft Report, December 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Preliminary Launch Site Processing Assessment - Space Station Flight Telerobotic Servicer (SSFTS), June 22, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- KSC MB-1 Processing Flow - GSFC/KSC Bilateral Meeting, June 22, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- FTS/APAE Memoranda and Information, July 11, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- FTS/APAE Information and Diagram, July 11, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer to Space Station Freedom Interface Control Document - Preliminary, June 1, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer to Mobile Servicing Centre Interface Control Document - Preliminary, June 1, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- MIR - FTS Interview, April 19, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Space Station Attached Payload Pointing System Options Study - Pointing System Design Concept and Performance Analysis White Paper, June 15, 1989 - Includes Letter on Report from Robert L. Staehle to Dr. Phillip Cressy, August 14, 1989, June 15, 1989, August 14, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer (FTS) Monthly Status Review, July 20, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Space Station: Leadership for the Future by Franklin D. Martin and Terence T. Finn, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Space Station: A Research Laboratory in Space, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Space Station/Space Station - Attached Payload Pointing Accommodation Study - White Papers, February 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- NASDA (National Space Development Agency of Japan) Informational Report, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Delta - 1960 - 1980 - America's Busiest and Most Versatile Launch Vehicle, circa 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Studying the Earth from Space Pamphlet, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Committee Print - The National Space Program - Present and Future - A Compilation of Papers Prepared for the Subcommittee on NASA Oversight of the Committee on Science and Astronautics U.S. House of Representatives - Ninety-First Congress - Second Session - Serial U, December 10, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- NASA 1958-1983 - Remembered Images, circa 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- National Aeronautics and Space Act of 1958, As Amended and Related Legislation, July 1, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Committee Print - Astronauts and Cosmonauts Biographical and Statistical Data - Report Prepared for the Committee on Science and Technology U.S. House of Representatives Ninety-Fourth Congress - First Session By The Science Policy Research Division Congressional Research Service - Library of Congress - Serial E, June 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Committee Print - Apollo Program Management - Staff Study for the Subcommittee on NASA Oversight of the Committee on Science and Astronautics U.S. House of Representatives - Ninety-First Congress - First Session - Serial C, July 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Vanguard - A History by Constance McLaughlin Green and Milton Lomask, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Apollo 15 - Preliminary Science Report, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- NASA Facts - Space Shuttle Fold Out Informational Poster, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- IEEE Spectrum Magazine - Special Issue - Communications: onward to the 80s, October 1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Review and Assessment of the U.S. Space Program by Homer E. Newell, May 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Speech by Dr. James C. Fletcher Administrator National Aeronautics on Space Administration to the Twenty-fifth Annual Conference Aerospace Industries Association, Williamsburg, VA., May 20, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Post Launch SL-1/SL-2 - Skylab Mission Operation Report, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Space Flight Record - 1958-1970, December 31, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Early Private Ventures - McDonnell Douglas Astronautics Company, October 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- A Cost History of the Thor-Delta Launch Vehicle Family by E.W. Bonnett, September 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 2 - Remote Sensing of Earth Resources - Educational Reports, May 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 3 - Materials Science - Educational Report, May 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 4 - Life Sciences - Educational Report, May 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- The Space Applications Program, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Skylab Earth Resources Data Catalog, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Future NASA Space Programs - Hearing Before The Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences United States Senate - Ninety-First Congress - First Session, August 5, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- The Space Program in the Post-Apollo Period - A Report of the President's Science Advisory Committee, February 1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- An Administrative History of NASA - 1958-1963, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Committee Print - Space Law- - Selected Basic Documents - Staff Report Prepared For the Use of the Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences - United States Senate, December 30, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences - United States Senate - Tenth Anniversary, 1958-1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Report of the Central Review Committee - Useful Applications of Earth - Oriented Satellites, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Priorities For Space Research - 1971-1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Skylab - A Guidebook, circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- OLS Project - Thanks for the Memories Informational Pamphlet - 1958-1998, circa 1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Memorandum Concerning and Attached to Science and Our Future - Address by Homer E. Newell - Associate Administrator - NASA, December 30, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Letter from Howard J. Lewis to Dr. George M. Low Concerning Discussion of Science Policy, January 5, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Management Scheme for Apollo, circa 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- What the Space Program Has Told Us About the Moon by Homer E. Newell, February 12, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- The Next Fifty Years Pamphlet by Dr. Hugh L. Dryden, July 1953 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- India Magazine Article, September, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Comparisons - First Wright Flight and Apollo II - Saturn 5 Flight, circa 1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Apollo Program - Interesting Information - Saturn V, circa 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Apollo Briefs, circa 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Man in Space - The Management Challenge, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Spacecraft Information and Diagrams, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Apollo Program - Interesting Information - Lunar Module, Apollo Spacecraft General, Command and Service Module, General, Space Program General, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Typed Page on NASA's Use of Computers, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Symposium on Significant Results Obtained From Earth Resources Technology Satellite-1 - Volume II - Summary of Results, March 5-9, 1973, May 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Earth Observations From Space - Binder, March 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Delta - A Legacy of Successful Adaptation, September 14-15, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- In Folder - Satellite System Documents, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- In Folder - Includes Documents on Tracking and Data Relay Satellite System (TDRSS), 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Putting Space to Work - Annual Report of the NASA Office of Applications, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Report to the Congress - A Metric America - A decision whose time has come, July 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- "In This Decade..." - Mission to the Moon Booklet, circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Hughes Multispectral Scanner System For Erts - Goddard Space Flight Center, circa 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- What's New on the Moon? Booklet, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Five Year Plan - Office of Applications - Presentation: August 15, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Space Shuttle Report, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)